Black Sparrow Press Collection, 1966-1994 (bulk 1973-1993)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Book Files, 1973-1993
  - #285 Dionysus and the Beat, Everson, William, Manuscript, Correspondence, Copy, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - #286 Spending Christmas with the Man from Receiving at Sears, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - #286 Spending Christmas with the Man from Receiving at Sears, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - #286 Spending Christmas with the Man from Receiving at Sears, Wakoski, Diane, Proofs, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - #286 Spending Christmas with the Man from Receiving at Sears, Wakoski, Diane, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1 Unbound, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - #287 In a Lost World, Roditi, Edouard, Manuscript, Proofs, Correspondence, Copy, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - #288 Seeking Air, Guest, Barbara, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - #288 Seeking Air, Guest, Barbara, First Draft, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - #288 Seeking Air, Guest, Barbara, Final Draft, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - #288 Seeking Air,, Guest, Barbara, Hardcover Copies, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - #289 You Kissed Lilly,, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Correspondence, Illustrations, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - #289 You Kissed Lilly,, Bukowski, Charles, Proofs, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - #289 You Kissed Lilly,, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover Copies, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - #290 Battles in Spain by Cesar Vallejo, translated by Eshleman, Clayton, and Barcia, Jose Rubia, Manuscript, Proof, Correspondence, Copy, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - #291 This Will Kill That, Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, Proof, Correspondence, Copy, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - #292 The Convections, Kelly, Robert, Artwork, Manuscript, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - #292 The Convections, Kelly, Robert, Artwork, 2 Hardcovers, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - #293 Break-up of our Camp: Stories, Artwork, notes, 1932, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - #293 Break-up of our Camp: Stories, Correspondence, 1932, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - #293 Break-up of our Camp: Stories, Manuscript, 1932, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - #293 Break-up of our Camp: Stories, First Proof, 1932, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - #293 Break-up of our Camp: Stories, 2 Hardcover, 2 Softcover, 1932, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - #294 Birdscapes,with Seaside, Tarn, Nathaniel, Manuscript, Proof, Correspondence, Copy, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - #295 Primitive, Oppen, George, Artwork, Correspondence, Ephemera, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - #295 Primitive, Oppen, George, Proofs, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - #295 Primitive, Oppen, George,3 Hardcover, 2 Softcover, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - #296 At Their Word: Essays on the Arts of Language, Corman, Cid, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - #296 At Their Word: Essays on the Arts of Language, Corman, Cid, Manuscript, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - #296 At Their Word: Essays on the Arts of Language, Corman, Cid, Proof, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - #296 At Their Word: Essays on the Arts of Language, Corman, Cid, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - #297 Wheres, Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, Proof, Correspondence, Copy, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - #298 A Conversation with Hitler, Clark, Tom, Manuscript, Correspondence, Proofs, Copies, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - #299 Towards a New American Poetics, Faas, Ekbert, Artwork, Correspondence, Review, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - #299 Towards a New American Poetics, Faas, Ekbert, Manuscript, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - #299 Towards a New American Poetics, Faas, Ekbert, Proof, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - #299 Towards a New American Poetics, Faas, Ekbert, Uncorrected Proofs (Last five sections), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - #299 Towards a New American Poetics, Faas, Ekbert, Uncorrected Proofs (Final 4 sections), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - #299 Towards a New American Poetics, Faas, Ekbert, 2 Hardcover Copies, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, First Manuscript, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, Second Manuscript, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, Deleted Materials (second manuscript), 1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, Third Manuscript, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, Final Manuscript, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - #300 Meaning a Life,, Oppen, Mary, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - #301 What I Own, Stepanchev, Stephen, Manuscript, Proof, Correspondence, Copy, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - #302 The United States (1885-1915) Recitative, Reznikoff, Charles, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - #302 The United States (1885-1915) Recitative, Reznikoff, Charles, Manuscript, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - #302 The United States (1885-1915) Recitative, Reznikoff, Charles, First Proof, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - #302 The United States (1885-1915) Recitative, Reznikoff, Charles, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - #303 Pachelbel’s Canon, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence, Manuscript, Proof, Copy, Poems, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - #304 What She Means, Eshleman ,Clayton, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - #304 What She Means, Eshleman, Clayton, First Manuscript, #304 What She Means, Eshleman, Clayton, Second Manuscript; #304 What She Means, Eshleman, Clayton, Final Manuscript,; #304 What She Means, Eshleman, Clayton, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover,; 1978 (Box 41, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6)
  - #305 We’ll Take Them, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript, Proof, Copy, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - #306 The Veritable Years 1949-1966, Everson, William, Artwork, Correspondence, Proof, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - #306 The Veritable Years 1949-1966, Everson, William, First Draft, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - #306 The Veritable Years 1949-1966, Everson, William, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - #306 The Veritable Years 1949-1966, Everson, William, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - #306 The Veritable Years 1949-1966, Everson, William, 1 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - #306 The Veritable Years 1949-1966, Everson, William, 2 Hardcover, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - #307 What’s for Dinner?, Schuyler, James, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - #307 What’s for Dinner?, Schuyler, James, Manuscript, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - #307 What’s for Dinner?, Schuyler, James, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - #308 Sparrow 61-72, 1 Hardcover, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - #309 A Ceremonial: Stories 1936-1940, Goodman, Paul, Artwork, Unused materials, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - #309 A Ceremonial: Stories 1936-1940, Goodman, Paul, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - #310 When Things Get Tough on Easy Street, Clark, Tom, Correspondence, Artwork, Deleted Poems, Notes, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - #310 When Things Get Tough on Easy Street, Clark, Tom, Manuscript, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - #310 When Things Get Tough on Easy Street, Clark, Tom, First Proof, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - #310 When Things Get Tough on Easy Street, Clark, Tom, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - #311 A Bibliography of the Writings of Wydham Lewis, Morrow, Bradford and Lafourcade, Bernard, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - #311 A Bibliography of the Writings of Wydham Lewis, Morrow, Bradford and Lafourcade, Bernard, Artwork, Ephemera, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - #311 A Bibliography of the Writings of Wydham Lewis, Morrow, Bradford and Lafourcade, Bernard, Photo Sections, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - #311 A Bibliography of the Writings of Wydham Lewis, Morrow, Bradford and Lafourcade, Bernard, Crossing the Frontier, Artwork, Manuscript, Proof, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - #311 A Bibliography of the Writings of Wydham Lewis, Morrow, Bradford and Lafourcade, Bernard, 1 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - #311 A Bibliography of the Writings of Wydham Lewis, Morrow, Bradford and Lafourcade, Bernard, 2 Hardbound/Slipcased Special Numbered File Copies, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, First Draft (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, First Draft (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, First Corrections, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, Final Proofs (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, Final Proofs (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, 3 Hardcover (1 signed), 3 Softcover (1 Revised), 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - #312 Women, Bukowski, Charles, Promotional Poster. Black and White Photograph, Copywright: Ulvis Alberts and Joan Levine, 1983/1984—See Oversized Items, Box 298, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - #313 All the Good People I’ve Left Behind, Oates, Joyce Carol, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979, (1978) (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - #313 All the Good People I’ve Left Behind, Oates, Joyce Carol, Sentimental Journey, Corrected Copy, 1979, (1978) (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - #313 All the Good People I’ve Left Behind, Oates, Joyce Carol, Setting Copy (1 of 2), 1979, (1978) (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - #313 All the Good People I’ve Left Behind, Oates, Joyce Carol, Setting Copy (2 of 2), 1979, (1978) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - #313 All the Good People I’ve Left Behind, Oates, Joyce Carol, Manuscript, 1979, (1978) (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - #313 All the Good People I’ve Left Behind, Oates, Joyce Carol, 2 Hardcover, 1 Hardbound/Slipcased File Copy, 1979, (1978) (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - #314 The Joe Chronicles: Part 2, Owens, Rochelle, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979, (1978) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - #314 The Joe Chronicles: Part 2, Owens, Rochelle, Manuscript, 1979, (1978) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - #314 The Joe Chronicles: Part 2, Owens, Rochelle, First Proof, 1979, (1978) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - #314 The Joe Chronicles: Part 2, Owens, Rochelle, 2 Hardcover, 1979, (1978) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - #315 A Love Poem, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - #315 A Love Poem, Bukowski, Charles, Proof, Unbound copy, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - #315 A Love Poem, Bukowski, Charles, Proof,2 Hardcover, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - #316 The Love Child, Shellnutt, Eve, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - #316 The Love Child, Shellnutt, Eve, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - #316 The Love Child, Shellnutt, Eve, Deleted Materials (from Manuscript), 1979 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - #316 The Love Child, Shellnutt, Eve, First Proof, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - #316 The Love Child, Shellnutt, Eve, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - #317 This Flower Only Blooms Every Hundred Years, Jaffe, Sherril, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - #317 This Flower Only Blooms Every Hundred Years, Jaffe, Sherril, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - #317 This Flower Only Blooms Every Hundred Years, Jaffe, Sherril, Final Proof, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - #317 This Flower Only Blooms Every Hundred Years, Jaffe, Sherril, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Artwork, Notes, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Poems Not in Manuscript, (1978) (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Poems Not in Manuscript, Chomo-Uri Magazine (Vol IV, No 1), 1977 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Poems Not in Manuscript, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Poems Not in Manuscript, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Poems Not in Manuscript, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Poems Not in Manuscript (1974 and previous) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Final Manuscript, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, First Revised Copy, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, Final Revised Copy, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - #318 Mad Dog Black Lady, Coleman, Wanda, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - #319 Collected Stories 1939-1976, Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Notes, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - #319 Collected Stories 1939-1976, Bowles, Paul, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - #319 Collected Stories 1939-1976, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - #319 Collected Stories 1939-1976, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - #319 Collected Stories 1939-1976, Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover, 2 Softcover, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - #320 Testimony: The United States (1885-1975) Recitative (Volume II), Reznikoff, Charles, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - #320 Testimony: The United States (1885-1975) Recitative (Volume II), Reznikoff, Charles, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - #321 Play the Piano Drunk Like a Percussion Instrument Until Your fingers Begin to bleed a Bit, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Correspondence, Ephemera, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - #321 Play the Piano Drunk Like a Percussion Instrument Until Your fingers Begin to bleed a Bit, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - #321 Play the Piano Drunk Like a Percussion Instrument Until Your fingers Begin to bleed a Bit, Bukowski, Charles, Proof, Unbound Copy, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - #321 Play the Piano Drunk Like a Percussion Instrument Until Your fingers Begin to bleed a Bit, Bukowski, Charles, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 58, Folger 4)
  - 1979 (Box 59, Folder 1, #322 Don Juan, Goodman, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes,)
  - #322 Don Juan, Goodman, Paul, First Proof, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - #322 Don Juan, Goodman, Paul, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - #322 Don Juan, Goodman, Paul, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - #323 Five Eyes by Abdeslam Boulaich, translated by Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - #323 Five Eyes by Abdeslam Boulaich, translated by Bowles, Paul, Revised Manuscript, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - #323 Five Eyes by Abdeslam Boulaich, translated by Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - #324 Trophies, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - #324 Trophies, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript and Deleted Material, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - #324 Trophies, Wakoski, Diane, Second Proof, Unbound Copy, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - #324 Trophies, Wakoski, Diane, 2 Hardcover, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - #325 Cybele, Oates, Joyce Carol, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - #325 Cybele, Oates, Joyce Carol, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - #325 Cybele, Oates, Joyce Carol, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1 Hardbound/Slip cased Copy, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - #326 The Facts of Life: Stories 1940-1949, Goodman, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - #326 The Facts of Life: Stories 1940-1949, Goodman, Paul, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - #326 The Facts of Life: Stories 1940-1949, Goodman, Paul, 1 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - #326 The Facts of Life: Stories 1940-1949, Goodman, Paul, 2 Hardcover, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - #327 Kill The Messenger Who Brings Bad News, Kelly, Robert, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - #327 Kill The Messenger Who Brings Bad News, Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - #328 Ask The Dust, Fante, John, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1980, (1979) (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - #328 Ask The Dust, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1980, (1979) (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - #328 Ask The Dust, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980, (1979) (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - #329 The Masks of Drought, Everson, William, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - #329 The Masks of Drought, Everson, William, Manuscript, Unbound Copy, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - #329 The Masks of Drought, Everson, William, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - #330 D.H. Lawrence and the High Temptation of the Mind, Olson, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, Proof, 2 Hardcover, 2 Softcover, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Journal of D.H. Lawrence Society, 1976, 1978; 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Lawrence County News: Newsletter of the D.H. Lawrence Society, 1976-1982 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - D.H. Lawrence of North America Newsletter: John Martin Membership Card, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - #331 The Beach Café and The Voice by Mohammed Mrabet, translated by Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Notes, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - #331 The Beach Café and The Voice by Mohammed Mrabet, translated by Bowles, Paul, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - #331 The Beach Café and The Voice by Mohammed Mrabet, translated by Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - #332 Notes on Aaron’s Rod, Miller, Henry, First Draft, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - #332 Notes on Aaron’s Rod, Miller, Henry, First Proof, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - #332 Notes on Aaron’s Rod, Miller, Henry, Second Proof, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - #332 Notes on Aaron’s Rod, Miller, Henry, 2 Hardcover, 1 Hardbound/Slip cased Signed Copy, 1 Unbound Copy with Hardcover, 1 Hardcover, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - #333 Cap of Darkness, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, Notes, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - #333 Cap of Darkness, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - #333 Cap of Darkness, Wakoski, Diane, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - #334 Ted Hughes: The Unaccommodated Universe, Faas, Ekbert, Artwork, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - #334 Ted Hughes: The Unaccommodated Universe, Faas, Ekbert, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - #334 Ted Hughes: The Unaccommodated Universe, Faas, Ekbert, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - #334 Ted Hughes: The Unaccommodated Universe, Faas, Ekbert, 1 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - #334 Ted Hughes: The Unaccommodated Universe, Faas, Ekbert, 2 Hardcover copies, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - #335 Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence, Volume I, edited by Butterick, George, Artwork, Negatives, Photographs, Correspondence, Notes, First Draft (Discarded Materials), 1980 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - #335 Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence, Volume I, edited by Butterick, George, Manuscript, Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence, Volume I, edited by Butterick, George, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover; 1980 (Box 67, Folder 3, Folder 4)
  - #336 Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence, Volume II, edited by Butterick, George, Artwork, Photographs, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - #336 Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence, Volume II, edited by Butterick, George, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - #336 Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence, Volume II, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - #337 The Last Gas Station and Other Stories, Clark, Tom, Artwork, Negative, Correspondence, Notes, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - #337 The Last Gas Station and Other Stories, Clark, Tom, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - #337 The Last Gas Station and Other Stories, Clark, Tom, 3 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - #338 The Galley to Mytilene, Stories 1949-1960: volume IV of the Collected Stories, Goodman, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - #338 The Galley to Mytilene, Stories 1949-1960: volume IV of the Collected Stories, Goodman, Paul, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - #338 The Galley to Mytilene, Stories 1949-1960: volume IV of the Collected Stories, Goodman, Paul, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, Artwork, Photographs, Negatives, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, Correspondence, Notes, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, First Draft, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, First Draft, (Discarded Materials), 1980 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, First Proof, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - #339 Letters to Christopher, Spender, Stephen, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - #340 Let It Come Down, Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - #340 Let It Come Down, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 2, Folder 3)
  - #340 Let It Come Down, Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - #341 Hades in Manganese, Eshleman, Clayton, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - #341 Hades in Manganese, Eshleman, Clayton, First Draft (Discarded Materials), 1981 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - #341 Hades in Manganese, Eshleman, Clayton, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - #341 Hades in Manganese, Eshleman, Clayton, 2 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - #342 Three Penny Lane, Dawson, Fielding, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - #342 Three Penny Lane, Dawson, Fielding, First Draft (Discarded Materials), 1981 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - #342 Three Penny Lane, Dawson, Fielding, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - #342 Three Penny Lane, Dawson, Fielding, 2 Hardcover v, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - #343 The Sea-Mists of the Winter, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Artwork, Copy, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - #343 The Sea-Mists of the Winter, Lewis, Wyndham,2 Hardcover copies, 2 Softcover, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, Artwork, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, Photographs, Negatives, Captions, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, Ephemera, Correspondence, Notes, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, Manuscript (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, Manuscript (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, Manuscript (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - #344 Bibliography of the Black Sparrow Press, Morrow, Bradford and Cooney, Seamus, 2 Trade Hardcover Copy, 1 Special Hardbound, 1 Hardbound/Slipcase File, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - #345 Proud Beggars by Albert Cossery translated by Cushing, Thomas, Artwork, Negatives, Correspondence, Notes, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)